David Barr

507 Cassia Way Arlington, TX 76002

davidmbarr@gmail.com

972-658-9710

Summary: Two years of the pandemic and other changes in my life over that time have made me realize something. Despite being incredibly passionate for music, and the teaching of music, it's no longer keeping me where I'd like to be financially. Deciding to switch has been an incredibly difficult decision, but a necessary one I feel.

I've been educating myself in the field of project management this past year, but that career path is not set in stone. I am open to other fields and opportunities that have the potential to help me fulfill my personal and financial goals in my life. I'm open to sales positions, account management positions, really anything in which the soft-skills I have acquired would help me excel.

Work Experience:

<u>Freelance Musician, October 2012-Present</u>: Private lesson and master class instructor for multiple school districts throughout the Dallas/Ft. Worth metroplex. Responsibilities included, contacting parents of potential students, schedule and teach the lessons, collect monthly payments from each parent.

Associate, The UPS Store November 2020-April 2021: Operated a register as in a retail setting. Took packages, made shipping labels, packed shipments, assisted customer with technical issues with the UPS website and tracking, answered store phone, organized mail for box-holders, perform other office-related services for customers, organized store and kept clean.

<u>Retail Associate, Staples June 2018-August 2019</u>: Worked the floor of a retail store. Operated cash register, stocked shelves, received shipments. Upsold items on the floor and helped customers find items, etc.

<u>Valet Attendant, Lone Star Parking, LLC August 2013-February 2016</u>: Worked as a parking attendant, handling large volumes of customer vehicles with care and attention.

Education:

Master's Degree in Music-2016 UT Arlington

Bachelor's in Music-2012

UT Arlington

Skills: Customer Service ~2 years

Retail Sales ~2 years

Microsoft Office Google Docs Windows Mac OSX 80 WPM

Certifications/Licenses:

Google Professional Certificates: Project Management

References Available Upon Request